(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,a){},14:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),c=a.n(n),o=a(7),r=a.n(o),s=(a(13),a(5)),i=a(4),l=a(2),u=[{id:0,question:"NgRX uses the RxJS observables for Angular",options:["True","False"],answer:"True",type:"radio"},{id:1,question:"React Hooks were introduced in replacement for React Classes?",options:["True","False"],answer:"True",type:"radio"},{id:2,question:"Select the only language that browsers can understand",options:["JavaScript","Java","C#","Pascal","PHP"],answer:"JavaScript",type:"radio"},{id:3,question:"NodeJS is a runtime environment for JavaScript and not a separate language",options:["True","False"],answer:"True",type:"radio"},{id:4,question:"Which of the following is a templating language for JavaScript?",options:["EJS","JQuery","React","Ruby"],answer:"EJS",type:"radio"},{id:5,question:"FANG is consisted of which American technology companies?",options:["Facebook","Amazon","Netflix","Google","Adobe","Apple","Accenture","Nokia"],answer:["Facebook","Amazon","Netflix","Google"],type:"checkbox"},{id:6,question:"Which of the following technologies are backend frameworks?",options:["Django","Vue","EmberJS","Laravel","Spring"],answer:["Django","Laravel","Spring"],type:"checkbox"},{id:7,question:"The MERN stack is consisted of which technologies?",options:["MongoDB","Express","React","NodeJS","EmberJS","MySQL","EJS","Ruby on Rails"],answer:["MongoDB","Express","React","NodeJS"],type:"checkbox"},{id:8,question:"The LAMP stack is consisted of which technologies?",options:["Linux","Apache","MySQL","PHP","Angular","MongoDB"],answer:["Linux","Apache","MySQL","PHP"],type:"checkbox"}],m=function(e){var t=e.quiz,a=e.handleSelection,o=e.userAnswer,r=e.currentQuestion,s=e.QuizData,i=e.handleNavigation,l=e.handleSubmission,u=e.type;return Object(n.useEffect)((function(){console.log(t)}),[]),c.a.createElement("div",{className:"card",style:{}},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"card-body"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-between"},c.a.createElement("h5",{className:"card-title"},t.question),c.a.createElement("p",{className:"counter"},"".concat(r+1," out of ").concat(s.length))),c.a.createElement("form",null,t&&"radio"===u&&t.options.map((function(e){return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-check p-0",key:e,onChange:function(){return a(t.id,e)}},c.a.createElement("input",{className:"form-check-input",type:"radio",name:e,id:t.question+e,value:t.question+e,checked:o[t.id]===e,readOnly:!0}),c.a.createElement("label",{className:"form-check-label btn btn-outline-secondary w-100 my-1",htmlFor:t.question+e},e))})),t&&"checkbox"===u&&t.options.map((function(e){return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-check p-0",key:e},c.a.createElement("input",{className:"form-check-input",type:"checkbox",name:e||"",id:e,value:e,checked:o[t.id]&&Array.isArray(o[t.id])&&o[t.id].includes(e),readOnly:!0}),c.a.createElement("label",{onClick:function(){return a(t.id,e)},className:"form-check-label btn btn-outline-secondary w-100 my-1",htmlFor:t.question+e},e))}))),c.a.createElement("div",{className:"buttons mt-3"},0!==r?c.a.createElement("a",{className:"previous btn btn-info text-white",onClick:function(){return i(-1)}},"Previous"):"",r<s.length-1?c.a.createElement("a",{className:"next btn btn-info text-white",onClick:function(){return i(1)}},"Next"):c.a.createElement("a",{className:"next btn btn-info text-white",onClick:function(){return l()}},"Submit All Answers"))))},d=function(e){var t=e.handleAgainBtn,a=(e.correctAnswers,e.QuizData,(0,e.calcPercentage)());return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"Results card"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"card-body text-center"},c.a.createElement("h4",{className:"card-title"},"Your result was : ",c.a.createElement("span",null,Math.round(a),"%")),100===a?c.a.createElement("h2",{className:"text-success"},"Ace!!!"):a>=85?c.a.createElement("h2",{className:"text-success"},"Excellent!"):a>=75?c.a.createElement("h2",{className:"text-success"},"Very Good!"):a>=60?c.a.createElement("h2",{className:"text-success"},"Good!"):a>=50?c.a.createElement("h2",{className:"text-success"},"You pass!"):c.a.createElement("h2",{className:"text-danger"},"You failed ;("),c.a.createElement("a",{className:"btn btn-info text-white my-3",onClick:function(){t()}},"Try again!")))},h=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)({}),t=Object(l.a)(e,2),a=t[0],o=t[1],r=Object(n.useState)(0),h=Object(l.a)(r,2),p=h[0],f=h[1],b=Object(n.useState)({question:"",options:[],answer:"",id:""}),y=Object(l.a)(b,2),g=y[0],E=y[1],N=Object(n.useState)(!1),w=Object(l.a)(N,2),v=w[0],k=w[1],x=function(e){var t,a,n=e.length;if(n)for(;--n;)t=e[a=Math.floor(Math.random()*(n+1))],e[a]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e},A=function(e,t){if(!Array.isArray(e)||!Array.isArray(t)||e.length!==t.length)return!1;for(var a=e.concat().sort(),n=t.concat().sort(),c=0;c<a.length;c++)if(a[c]!==n[c])return!1;return!0},S=function(e){setTimeout((function(){f(p+e)}),50)},q=function(){k(!0)};Object(n.useEffect)((function(){console.log(u),x(u),u.forEach((function(e){return x(e.options)}))}),[]),Object(n.useEffect)((function(){p<u.length&&E({id:u[p].id,question:u[p].question,options:Object(i.a)(u[p].options),answer:u[p].answer})}),[p]);return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},c.a.createElement("h1",{className:"display-4 mb-4  mt-3 text-center"},"Quiz App"),v?c.a.createElement(d,{handleAgainBtn:function(){k(!1),f(0),o(""),p<u.length&&E({id:u[p].id,question:u[p].question,options:Object(i.a)(u[p].options),answer:u[p].answer})},QuizData:u,calcPercentage:function(){for(var e=0,t=u.map((function(e){return e.id})),n=0;n<u.length;n++)(Array.isArray(a[t[n]])&&A(a[t[n]],u[n].answer)||a[t[n]]===u[n].answer)&&e++;return e/u.length*100}}):"radio"===u[p].type?c.a.createElement(m,{quiz:g,handleSelection:function(e,t){var n=Object(s.a)({},a);n[e]=t,o(n)},userAnswer:a,currentQuestion:p,QuizData:u,handleNavigation:S,handleSubmission:q,type:"radio"}):c.a.createElement(m,{quiz:g,handleSelection:function(e,t){var n=Object(s.a)({},a);a[e]&&Array.isArray(a[e])?n[e].includes(t)?n[e]=n[e].filter((function(e){return e!==t})):n[e]=[].concat(Object(i.a)(a[e]),[t]):n[e]=[t],o(n)},userAnswer:a,currentQuestion:p,QuizData:u,handleNavigation:S,handleSubmission:q,type:"checkbox"}))};r.a.render(c.a.createElement(c.a.StrictMode,null,c.a.createElement(h,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},8:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(14)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.a94a91f0.chunk.js.map